This is a video that i have been waiting to make for an entire year.
(null)
Actually i hadn't really planned to quit smoking green for this long when i decided
to quit but.
Now here we are so let's take you back on this journey to my relationship
with the gunj why i quit.
And how it impacted my life since quitting it was sixth grade i was minding
my business just taking a piss in the middle school bathroom praying that no upperclassmen
would barge through the door and start heckling me about something that my social anxiety
couldn't handle my prayers were not answered and two eighth-graders that were in my sister's
class came in as loud as any to eighth-grade dudes running into the bathroom could
be i quickly noticed that they were my sister's friend's and put my head down
towards the urinal in the hopes that they wouldn't recognize me by my.
Harry potter shaped glasses from my left ear i heard one of them say yo
isn't that olivia's little brother by this time i had finished going pee and i
had nowhere to run as it my pants.
E n t e r   i n t o   t h e m .
Yeah that's me after a series of questions that i don't really remember they asked
me do you think you'll ever drink alcohol and i said probably then they asked
me do you think you'll ever smoke weed.
A n d   i   s a i d .
Probably not boy was i wrong about my alcohol in bud intake fast forward to
the end of eighth grade and my friend do i plan to hang out with
already comes over to my house with a strange-looking black bag in that black bag.
Was some green that he took from his dad's stash it was looking like it
was time for me to take my first hit ever i told my sister about
what was in this black no smell back because she obviously had a lot more
experience than me and she quickly made a device made out of a gatorade bottle
i'm not going to say what that thing actually is in the hopes that you
guys can guess what she started my 6-year relationship with the sticky stuff by the
time freshman year of high school started i would do it pretty much every single
day i remember that you're specifically every friday night after ski club i would lock
myself in my room.
T h r o w   a   t o w e l   u n d e r   m y   d o o r .
Do it out of my bedroom window and get under the covers to watch the
latest workaholics episode it was definitely one of the stoner kids i was one of
the.
First kids in my class to do it frequently the green stuff became a part
of my identity but when you start to rip green that much and you do
it that often you really don't realize how it's affecting your life that is not
until you decide to quit.
B e f o r e   t h i s   3 6 5 - d a y .   i   h a d   n e v e r   w a n t e d   t o   q u i t .
I never made an effort to quit the longest that i had gone in the
six years that i have been cheaping was 30 days when i decided to go
sober for a month about 2 years ago but one year ago a lot in
my life was changing i was doing a lot of different things to try and
improve my life in my life situation it was around the same time that i
pretty much stopped drinking alcohol completely and i started doing no fat in these first
couple months it was definitely hard to resist the temptation of wanting to do and
really out.
Everything sleeping was the biggest pain i had a much harder time actually falling asleep
and then when i did fall asleep.
T h e   d r e a m s   w e r e .
Absolutely crazy i'm pretty sure that for some people if they smoke they can still
dream but i never did and especially if i did it right before bed then
i wouldn't even have like.
Any memory of any dreams so when i was finally not smoking every night before
bed.
The dreams were extremely vivid and so vivid to the point where sometimes the first
half of the day i'd be like messed up from the dream that i had
i'm not sure exactly when that one away i didn't really keep a log of
all the things that were happening after i quit but i would say that those
really vivid dreams that would kind of messed me up a stopped after like a
few weeks or so he'll let me tell you how this has impacted this entire
past year and why i think this has played such a huge role.
I n   m y   s u c c e s s e s   y e a r   t h r o u g h   y o u t u b e   t h r o u g h   m y   b u s i n e s s   a n d   p r e t t y   m u c h .
Every other facet of my life i want to preface this by saying i know
that green effect.
E v e r y b o d y   d i f f e r e n t l y   i ' m   j u s t   s h a r i n g   m y   p e r s o n a l   e x p e r i e n c e   s o .
K e e p   t h a t   i n   m i n d   b e f o r e   y o u   d e c i d e   t o   g o   t o   t h e   c o m m e n t s   a n d   s a y .
Oh no bro i can smoke all day and i can get something done and
i'm happy and i'm productive and it was lacks as me and it makes me
happy okay man i first let's talk about energy levels the amount of consistent energy
that i have on a daily basis now is mindblowing to me compared to a
couple years ago so not like i was high all day everyday sometimes i would
wake and bake yes.
B u t   m o s t   o f   t h e   t i m e .
I was smoking anywhere between 3 and 5 p.m. and after doing that it was
just harder to get stuff done i remember i used to try and work out
while i was high to justify me smoking.
And every time i would work out it just wasn't as good as a workout
now i can function with much higher energy levels throughout the day and with less
sleep to.
Because i personally have felt like my sleep quality has improved and we all know
sleep dictates every other area of your life when you're awake now i can see
how coming off of it at first maybe the first few months or so who
would make you more tired than when you do it because you got sort of
a mental dependency on it from just doing it every single day after you get
over that hump i think you experience what i experienced which was higher energy level
another thing that happened when i quit that.
Was really hard for me to accept was that a kind of showed me who
my true friends were many times in the past i had this battle in my
head of a my going to hang out with this person because i genuinely enjoy
hanging out with them and i want to go over to their house to you
know have fun and do whatever.
O r   i s   i t   b e c a u s e .
That they're providing some sort of escape for me from what i actually need to
do.
And that escape was the greek i still hang out with these people and i
love them to death.
But now i know that a lot of the times that i was doing this
going over my friends house.
Just to smoke it made me kind of question if i wanted to see these
people really as much as i was seeing them related to that i think quitting
really helped me to cut out all the b******* in my life i think that
the gods really allowed me to bull.
Myself in a lot of different areas of life and made me think in some
situations i you know i've done enough with my day i can take the rest
of the day off i can just chill and do nothing and i knew that
i needed to do more if i wanted to really get to where i wanted
to be in life.
I   h a d   t o   p u t   i n   m o r e   w o r k   t h a n   i   w a s .
And quitting that just allowed me to stop both thing with myself it did not
make me more creative i feel.
Far more creative now and have more creative ideas now that i'm off of it
didn't really relax me like i told myself it did like i would have panic
attacks quite a bit.
When i was high i mean it was just like a total escape method for
escaping what i actually needed to do and who i actually needed to be in
with that i feel that.
Quitting has also allowed me to be more in tune with my real authentic self
i'm just like a completely different person when i'm on it less emotions less.
Passion for life less hunger to do things that i know will better me my
life no longer feels like someone else is living it after 3 to 5 p.m.
when i would do it like waking and baking was so it's so stupid of
me thinking about it now it's like.
Wow you just started your day and you completely wasted it would look really performing
at a high level having to record write youtube scripts.
Coach people without content yeah let's see you do that and i would never ever
really do it that well so yes quitting it's made me have higher productivity i
love what i do i love working for most of the day honestly that's really
what my days consist of now but it doesn't.
F e e l   l i k e   w o r k .
And i know that i'm not going to ever try to escape my work around
3 to 5 p.m. because i think i deserve it and then try to be
productive after it which i just.
Wasn't like i've done a lot of my edits and a lot of my videos
in the past while i was high and i just don't think they turned out
as well like my god man.
Being sober is so underrated i never thought that i would be saying something like
that something else that came with it was just being way more sociable i talk
about this in a previous video about how at parties or social situations you know
everybody's doing it.
They hand me that there like you want to take your head and i'm like
yeah because.
I want a more sociable and feel like i fit in and have something to
relate with all these people.
But then you hit it and you become more socially awkward than you were before
hitting and you think it's going to help you.
And it doesn't that's kind of what sums up my whole experience with green i
can tell you that smoking has kept me from a ton of opportunities because those
opportunities.
Required me to get out in social situations and when i smoked you i got
really.
C a n   i   t h e   p o i n t   w h e r e   w a s   t o u g h .
Talking to people and so i declined many opportunities or situations where i would have
to talk to people and now you know i'm much more extroverted i'm up.
More confident in myself i was way less confident when i was high on stanley
thing about what is everyone thinking of me am i saying the wrong thing those.
Things really were amplified when i was high i was still getting high everyday there
is zero chance i would be able to put out as many videos as i
am now as i go to places like this and i get a lot of
b-roll and i just wouldn't feel up to it and also i'd get social anxiety
from the weed now i just don't have a problem talking to anybody so pretty
much anybody in all of these things happened because quitting green vastly improved my mental
health i'm no longer using weed to deal with my problems anymore or as an
escape or as an excuse for something or two bullet myself i deal with my
problems naturally.
And in a healthy way i don't use it as a coping mechanism anymore and
using the ganja as much as i was made me feel worse about myself over
all i can think about this so clearly.
Now that i've been off it for so long like the amount of negative thoughts
that i had on a daily basis was doubled if not tripled compared to what
it is now because i feel better about myself because i feel like my real
self and i feel fresh.
And energized all the time and i'm not in that we'd stayed half of the
day then i can get what i need to get done always i can always
know that what i'm doing is my true self and i can do it with
a lot of energy look i'm sure that there's some sort of middle ground here.
F r o m   n o t   s m o k i n g   w e e d   a t   a l l .
T o   s m o k i n g   e v e r y   s i n g l e   d a y .
I don't need it no part of me wants to do it anymore i have
no sort of itch to do it recently i had a buddy of mine just
asked me straight up.
Y o u   k n o w   w h y   d o n ' t   y o u   s m o k e .
W e e d   a n y m o r e   a n d .
If i could summon up in just one sentence this is what i told him
i said that i want to be able to perform at the highest level possible
in anything i do whether that's fitness weather that's in terms of business what i
do right now.
T a l k i n g   t o   p e o p l e   w o r k   o u t p u t .
E n e r g y   a n d   w e e d .
Does absolutely nothing but hinder all of that i'm really not kidding with myself anymore
and i realize that it does nothing but hinder that.
W h y   w o u l d   i   d o   i t   i   j u s t .
D o n ' t   w a n t   t o   d o   i t   t h a n k   y o u   t o   a l l   t h e   p a t r o n s   o n   t h i s   c h a n n e l .
Patreon this is a platform where i'm putting out exclusive videos blog post and podcast
that you can't find anywhere else that's also where you can talk to me one-on-one
over the phone if you want to check that out the link is in the
description to patreon.com cole hastings thank you so much for watching till the end let
me know what you thought and goodbye have a good rest of your day or
night.